{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "3 About half of your diet should be made up of __________.",
            "option1": "Grains And Vegetables",
            "option2": "Fruits And Milk",
            "option3": "Milk And Cheese",
            "option4": "Fats And Sugars",
            "answer": "Grains And Vegetables"
        },

        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "5 This food group is our body's best source of energy?",
            "option1": "Meat Group",
            "option2": "Fats,Oils And Sweets",
            "option3": "Breads And Cereals",
            "option4": "Milk And Cheese",
            "answer": "Breads And Cereals"
        },

        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "7 The bread, cereal, rice and pasta group is a good source of _______?",
            "option1": "carbohydrate",
            "option2": "vitamin C",
            "option3": "calcium",
            "option4": "vitamin D",
            "answer": "carbohydrate"
        },

        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "8 Foods from the meat, poultry, fish dry beans, eggs and nuts group are an important source of ________?",
            "option1": "Iron",
            "option2": "Fiber",
            "option3": "Beta Carotene",
            "option4": "Calcium",
            "answer": "Iron"
        },

        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "The milk, cheese & yogurt group are important for ________?",
            "option1": "Strong Bones",
            "option2": "Teeth",
            "option3": "Muscles",
            "option4": "All Of The Above",
            "answer": "All Of The Above"
        },

        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "How many servings of vegetables do we need each day?",
            "option1": "6-11",
            "option2": "2-3",
            "option3": "3-5",
            "option4": "1-2",
            "answer": "3-5"
        },

        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "4 Milk, cheese and eggs are the sources of",
            "option1": "Vitamin C and A",
            "option2": "Vitamin A and D",
            "option3": "Vitamin C and D",
            "option4": "Vitamin B and C",
            "answer": "Vitamin A and D"
        },

        {
            "id":8,
            "question": "13 Which of the following has the highest calorific value ?",
            "option1": "Carbohydrates",
            "option2": "Fats",
            "option3": "Proteins",
            "option4": "Vitamins",
            "answer": "Fats"
        },

        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "16 Which of the following is considered an easily digestible source of protein?",
            "option1": "Egg albumin",
            "option2": "Soyabean",
            "option3": "Fish flesh",
            "option4": "Red meat",
            "answer": "Soyabean"
        },

        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "8 Which of the following works with calcium to build strong bones",
            "option1": "Vitamin D",
            "option2": "Vitamin C",
            "option3": "Phosphorus",
            "option4": "Iron",
            "answer": "Vitamin D"
        }
    ]
}